Lucas Luz

Full-Stack Web Developer



- Portuguese
- Amsterdam, NL in Icalazansl
- 🔘 Icalazansi 🔭 Iluz.dev
- ☑ lucas@calazansluz.com

Skills

HMTL | SCSS | JS Ruby | Rails | React SOL | Git Hub | Git G-Suite | Mac | PS

Work Experience

Catering Manager @ Google Amsterdam,

Vermaat Apr 2018 - May 2022 Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Asst. Catering Manager @ Google São Paulo,

Food+ by Compass Feb 2017 - Mar 2018 São Paulo, Brazil

Customer Success Specialist, Practo 🖸 2015 - 2016 São Paulo, Brazil

About Me

After living in the Netherlands for the past four years, I've decided to pursue my love for technology by completing Le Wagon's Fullstack Bootcamp. You can find my latest projects on my GitHub or website as I keep working to improve myself and my work.

I have over ten years of experience managing international teams and events. More recently, I have been responsible for a tech giant's internal catering services and external events in Amsterdam.

Latest Projects

HomeBar App, Ruby | HTML | SCSS | JS ☑

This App is like having a bartender at your fingertips. Select the ingredients you have at home, so the app tells which cocktails you can make, or are just a few ingredients away from.

- Project owner and lead
- · Designed, implemented and tested the algorithm
- · Devise and other gems integrated

Freddie's Fiets, Ruby | HTML | SCSS | JS ☑

My first full-stack project ever is a marketplace to rent or lease a bike.

- JS for navbar transition and typed JS
- Seeding, Cloudinary and Mapbox API
- Full-Stack development

Education

Full-Stack Web Developer | Bootcamp, Le Wagon 🗷

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022 | Amsterdam, The Netherlands

A ten-week Bootcamp that, focuses on **Software Architecture**, Relational DB - SQL, OOP, Ruby on Rails, JS, and invent, pitch, design, code, and deploy a project during the two final weeks.

Marketing Management | MBA, Insper ☑

2015 - 2016 | São Paulo, Brazil

From marketing research and customer behaviour to the breakdown of the marketing mix, as well as integrated communication and value creation through products and services.

Events Management | B. Tech, Anhembi Morumbi University 2012 – 2013 | São Paulo, Brazil

Canguages

Portuguese (Native) | English (Fluent) | Dutch (A2) | Spanish



Coffee | Cycling | Pets | Cocktails | Boardgames | Coding